You accomplished a lot in this first lesson. Starting with nothing more
than Android Studio and hope, you've created your first project. Built and
deployed it to virtual and actual devices, and
even created a simple list-based UI that's populated using an adapter.
You also learned a little about what makes mobile and Android, in particular,
a different environment to develop for the desktop, web, and server. But we've
only just gotten started. The app we've got so far is using static mock data.
So join us in lesson two to learn how to hook it up to real weather data.
But before that, take a moment to cleanse your palate with
a brief interlude exploring the history and evolution of the Android ecosystem.